Guide to the J. B. Fuqua Papers, 1929-2006 and undated RL.00426
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. B. Fuqua papers
1929-2006 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Fuqua, J. B., 1918-2006
RL.00426
70.9 Linear Feet
Businessman, philanthropist, and chairman of The Fuqua Companies and Fuqua Enterprises. The J.B. Fuqua Papers span the years 1929-2006. The collection is separated into two divisions according to place of origin: Fuqua's business office and his home office. The office files document Fuqua Industries and The Fuqua School of Business at Duke University, and include annual reports, reading files and general business papers, as well as clippings, periodicals, and copies of articles about J. B. Fuqua and his businesses. The home office files primarily document Fuqua's early career and contain files for the various businesses he acquired. A large component of video cassette recordings chiefly contain speeches and programs related to Fuqua and the Duke University Fuqua School of Business.
53,000 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All original audiovisual recordings are closed to use. Technical Services staff need to arrange to have use copies made before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. B. Fuqua Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in 2008 and 2019.
Biographical Note
Businessman, philanthropist, and chairman of The Fuqua Companies and Fuqua Enterprises.
Collection Overview
The J. B. Fuqua Papers span the years 1929 to 2006, with the bulk of the collection dating from the 1950s to the 1980s. The collection is separated into two divisions according to place of origin: files from Fuqua's business office and his home office. The office files document Fuqua Industries and The Fuqua School of Business at Duke University (founded by J.B. Fuqua), and include annual reports, reading files and general business papers, as well as clippings, periodicals and copies of articles about J. B. Fuqua and his businesses, and some photographs. The home office files primarily document Fuqua's early career and contain many files containing financial records and other materials pertaining to the various businesses he acquired. Fuqua owned several media outlets, including a television station, thus, a large group of materials contain correspondence, applications, and other business materials regarding Fuqua's media ventures and interactions with the Federal Communications Commission. A large component of video recordings chiefly relate to business programs with which Fuqua was involved, and the history of the Duke University Fuqua School of Business; many contain recordings of Fuqua's speeches. The original videos seem to have had a numerical identification system which was not recorded in this inventory. A small but significant group of videocassettes documents the development of Fuqua's program for managers in the former Soviet Union. There are also a number of scrapbooks and photographs, including publicity shots of Fuqua. Although Fuqua was active in Georgia politics, serving in the Georgia House of Representatives and the Georgia Senate, there appear to be relatively few records in the collection relating to this area of his life other than materials on Jimmy Carter and his family and some correspondence from other politicians.
Audiocassettes; Business management -- Soviet Union; Videocassettes; Philanthropy -- North Carolina; Philanthropists -- North Carolina; Photographs; Scrapbooks; Clippings (information artifacts); Duke University. Fuqua School of Business; Fuqua Industries; Duke University. Fuqua School of Business. Center for Soviet Management Development; Fuqua, J. B., 1918-2006
- Accession 2008-0024
  - Office Files
    - Files, 1940s (Box 1)
    - Files, 1960s (Box 2)
    - Files, 1960s (Box 3)
    - Office and Subject Files, 1970s-1990s (Box 4-7)
    - Reading files (bound) (Box 8)
    - Reading files (bound) (Box 9)
    - Reading files (bound) (Box 10)
    - Reading files, 1998-2000 (Box 11)
    - Reading files, 2000-2003 (Box 12)
    - Reading files, 2004-2006 (Box 13)
    - Office Files, 1997 (Box 13)
    - Office files, Fugua, Triton, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
    - Fuqua, Triton, 1978-1990 (Box 15)
    - Press files, 1980s (Box 16)
    - Press files, 1980s (Box 17)
    - Clippings (Box 18)
    - Clippings (Box 19)
    - Periodicals and Clippings (Box 20)
    - Philanthropic awards (Box 21)
    - Periodicals (Box 21)
    - Periodicals, 1983-1993 (Box 22)
    - Fuqua Industries Annual Reports, 1967-1972 (Box 23)
    - Fuqua Industries Annual Reports, 1972-1988 (Box 24)
    - Annual Reports, 1965-1973 (Box 25)
    - Annual Reports, 1973-1978 (Box 26)
    - Annual Reports, 1979-1989 (Box 27)
    - Annual Reports, 1967-1993 (Box 28)
    - Annual Reports, 1978-1995 (Box 29)
    - Annual Reports, 1972-2995 (Box 30)
    - Vista Annual Reports and Business Periodicals, 1976-1989 (Box 31)
    - Subsidiary Articles, 1982 (Box 32)
    - Annual Reports 1961-1970 (Box 32)
    - Fuqua articles, 1985 (Box 32)
    - Transmittal files, 1975-1976 (Box 33)
    - Reports, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Index of Fuqua Mailings, 1967-1974 (Box 34)
    - Subsidiary articles, 1984, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Subsidiary Articles, 1981 and 1988 (Box 35)
    - Team Spirit, 1970s-1980s (Box 36)
    - Articles, 1982 (Box 36)
    - To Do Lists, 1990-1997 (Box 36)
    - Articles, 1986-1988 (Box 37)
    - Going Private, 1981 (Box 37)
    - Fuqua address books, 1970s-1990s (Box 38)
    - Printed materials (Box 38)
    - Audio cassettes and video cassettes (Box 39)
    - Copies of Fortune (Box 40)
    - Clippings (Box 40)
    - Letters to Fuqua, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Film, 2 rolls (Box 40)
    - Slides (Box 41)
    - Subsidiary articles (Box 41)
    - Slides (Box 42)
    - Photographs (Box 42)
    - Subsidiary articles (Box 43)
    - Fuqua School of Business papers (Box 43)
    - Subsidiary articles (Box 44)
    - Fuqua School of Business papers (Box 44)
    - Slides (Box 44)
    - Subsidiary articles (Box 45)
    - Fuqua School of Business papers (Box 45)
    - Slides (Box 45)
    - Fuqua School of Business papers (Box 46)
    - Fuqua School of Business papers (Box 47)
    - Slides (Box 47)
    - Fuqua School of Business papers (Box 48)
    - Fuqua School of Business papers (Box 49)
    - Fuqua School of Business books, 1994-2004 (Box 50)
    - Fuqua School of Business, 1968-1996 (Box 51)
    - Bound Volumes
      Scope and Contents note
      Volumes contain information related to Fuqua Industries including mergers.
      - 1978 (Box 52)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 53)
      - 1972-1980 (Box 54)
      - 1968-1973 (Box 55)
      - 1973-1986 (Box 56)
      - 1968-1970 (Box 57)
      - 1973-1978 (Box 58)
      - 1970-1991 (Box 59)
      - 1970-1991 (Box 60)
  - Home Office Files
    - Personal/appointment diaries, 1962-1963 (Box 61)
    - Personal/appointment diaries, 1965-2005 (Box 61)
    - Reel to Reel tape from WGFS, Covington, Georgia (Box 61)
    - Assorted Programs with Fuqua's name (Box 61)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1936-1970 (Box 62)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1971-1978 (Box 63)
    - Agreement to Purchase Equipment from RCA, 1963 (Box 64)
    - Assorted material pertaining to radio station KCKN, Kansas City, 1961-1964 (Box 64)
    - Blueprint of office space in First National Bank Building, Atlanta (Box 64)
    - Business plan for acquiring controlling stock of Natco (a public company), 1965 (Box 64)
    - Specimen of Stock Purchase Warrant, Willingham Finance Co., Inc., 1952 (Box 64)
    - Warrant to Purchase Stock in Fuqua Industries, Inc. (John, Alan, and Dorothy Fuqua), 1970 (Box 64)
    - Completed Community Needs surveys by WJBF to community leaders, 1972, 12 items (Box 64)
      Community needs surveys required for FCC license renewal.
    - Correspondence, 1957-1967 (Box 64)
    - Appraisal of TV station KTVE, El Dorado, Arkansas, 1964, 2 copies (Box 64)
    - Photocopy of Augusta Herald with an article about Fuqua, 1957 (Box 64)
    - Appraisal of an office building in Augusta, Georgia, 1965, 2 copies (Box 64)
    - Appraisal of two TV stations owned by Fuqua, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Write up on Miraculous Growth of Fuqua Industries (Box 64)
    - Extract from Stockholders list of Great Lakes Industries, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Extract from Stockholders list of Natco, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Program for Golf Tournament Sponsored by Fuqua Industries and Jackie Gleason, 1975 (Box 64)
    - Appraisal Report of TV Properties owned by Fuqua Industries, Inc., 1965 (Box 64)
    - Appraisal Report of residential property in Augusta, Georgia, 1959 (Box 64)
    - Operating Expenses Report for KTVE, Inc., 1962 (Box 64)
    - Operating Statement Ledger for KTVE, Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 64)
    - KTVE, Inc. Balance Sheet for month of October, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Stock Purchase Agreement for Fuqua to buy Great Lakes Industries Stock, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Agreements to hold Natco Shares for sale to Fuqua for a period of three years, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Balance sheet reports of Fuqua Industries, its subsidiaries, and other companies, 1953-1967 (Box 64)
    - Structural Steel Specifications for Office and Studio Building, WJBF-TV (Box 64)
    - Census map of Counties of State of Georgia, 1960 (Box 64)
    - Preliminary Annual Report for Fuqua Industries, Inc., 1972 (Box 64)
    - Report on Royal Crown Bottling Co., Augusta, Georgia, in pursuit of loan, 1949 (Box 65)
    - Assorted material pertaining to radio station sales, 1960-1965 (Box 65)
    - Report on Audit, Radio Evansville WROZ, completed by Caddick, Gaither, and Harris, 1964 (Box 65)
    - UHF Folder (Box 65)
    - Harcourt, Brace & World, Inc. application to FCC for permit for new TV station in Augusta, and news clipping, 1966 (Box 65)
    - Special Invitation from Saint Augustine, Florida, for paid 4-day visit to the Fuqua family, 1965 (Box 65)
    - Financial Analyses of Georgia-Carolina Broadcasting Co for years 1954-1960 (Box 65)
    - Duebill Advertising (Box 65)
    - Correspondence RE: Hotel/Airline service in exchange for TV advertising, 1950-1962 (Box 65)
    - Educational TV, 1958-1962 (Box 65)
      Files on the use of TV in education and schools.
    - Audience Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 65)
    - Correspondence and files dealing with a fire that destroyed WJBF in 8/56 and efforts to relocate station and transmitter, 1957 (Box 66)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1957-1964 (Box 66)
      File containing materials re: Sales and Marketing for WJBF, including a 1957 letter to Senator Strom Thurmond arguing against the details a bill proposed by him.
    - American Research Bureau, Inc., files, 1955-1961 (Box 66)
    - KTVE (TV) files, 1964-1965 (Box 66)
      12/4/64 letter to General Manager Of KTVE stating for the record that KTVE will carry no programs… for the Communist Party, the Ku Klux Klan, or any similar organization…. AND a 12/19/64 thank you letter from U.S. Congressman Oren Harris.
    - J. B. Fuqua: President, Fuqua Industries Business Card (Box 66)
    - Balance Sheet Report for Georgia Carolina Broadcasting Co. by Victor Markwalter, 1961 (Box 66)
    - Augusta/Richmond County Human Relations Commission publication, 1973 (Box 66)
    - WPTR files, Albany, New York, 1953-54 (Box 66)
    - Correspondence on airing of Sports on WJBF, 1957-1961 (Box 66)
    - Louis Harris & Associates file: Survey on TV and the Gubernatorial Election, 1962 (Box 66)
    - Files about negotiations to buy TV stations, 1959-1962 (Box 67)
    - Balance Sheet Report for WROZ compiled by Caddick, Gaither and Hortin, CPA, 1965 (Box 67)
    - WFAK (Charleston, SC, Radio Station) file, 1947-1948 (Box 67)
    - Weather Instruments file of information and correspondence for weather forecast providers, 1960-1962 (Box 67)
    - Maps of WJBF-TV's Coverage area (Box 67)
    - Pictures file containing photographs pertaining to WJBF-TV and WROZ-Radio, 1955-1964 (Box 67)
    - Aircraft Owners and Pilots Association insurance underwriters certificate, 1967 (Box 67)
    - Balance sheets and Operating Statements for Fuqua Industries, Claussen's Inc., KTVE Inc., WJBF, and WTVW, 1965-1966 (Box 67)
    - Correspondence and materials protesting to a request by a station to change call letters to something similar to WJBF, 1968 (Box 67)
    - Surveys folder containing professionally prepared reports on radio/TV audiences, 1954-1963 (Box 67)
    - Stuckey's Pecan Shoppe, 1967-1970 (Box 68)
      Correspondence, statements of operations, and other materials.
    - Burger King account files, 1967-1970 (Box 68)
      Paid checks, bank statements, and associated materials.
    - 1967-1968 Corp. Income tax for Fuqua Investment Co. prepared by Victor Markwalter, 1967-1968 (Box 68)
    - John B. Fuqua Foundation, Inc. - Assorted financial materials (check stubs, 1099's, etc.), 1970-1971 (Box 68)
    - WJBF Financial Data Folder - Reports, Correspondences, Clippings, etc. related to WJBF, 1949-1966 (Box 68)
    - Atlanta (Pub of the Atlanta Chamber of Commerce), May 1968, Article on J.B. Fuqua, p. 22 (Box 68)
    - Twelve (12) copies of a Balance sheet report of Georgia Carolina Broadcasting Co, 6/30/1960 (Box 68)
    - Fuqua Investment Folder - Assorted materials RE: Fuqua Investment Company, 1953-1967 (Box 68)
      Small, early photo, probably of J. B. Fuqua.
    - Willingham Finance Company Folder - Assorted materials RE: Willingham Finance, 1955-1961 (Box 68)
    - Lease agreement to lease properties in Spartanburg from Burger King of South Carolina, Inc., 1966 (Box 68)
    - KTVE Sales graphs for 1961-1963 (Box 68)
    - J.B Fuqua Lock Box Inventory dated October 1965 (Box 68)
    - Letter to Gov. Carl Sanders stating that the Gov. has 1/3 interest in a joint account with Fuqua and Hester, 1964 (Box 68)
    - Willingham Finance Co. Resolution that Fuqua be given authority to sell and dispose of securities owned by the company as he sees fit and proper, 1959 (Box 69)
    - TV Financing Folder - assorted materials on profitability of TV and particular stations and financing ventures, 1951-1966 (Box 69)
    - CBS Folder - Assorted Correspondences and Materials RE: CBS affiliation and airing their programs, 1957-1960 (Box 69)
    - 1965 Annual Report of the Southeastern Broadcasting Corp, 1965 (Box 69)
    - FCC Publication #90562 Public Notice AM-FM Broadcast Financial Data -- 1965 (Box 69)
    - FCC Publication #74940 Public Notice AM-FM Broadcast Financial Data -- 1964 (Box 69)
    - American Research Bureau TV Circulation Study - August, Georgia, March 1964 (Box 69)
    - Harvard Business Review article Reprint, Ellis, Repurchase Stock to Revitalize Equity, 1965 (Box 69)
    - Martin Theatres Folder - Assorted Correspondences RE: dealing with Martin Theatres, 1954-1963 (Box 69)
    - Balance Sheet Folder - Containing Balance sheets of Fuqua Industries & other Co.s, 1956-1965 (Box 69)
    - Fuqua National Inc. Balance Sheets, 1968-1970 (Box 69)
    - Balance Sheet and other material related to Claussen's (Daisy Foods Inc.), 1969-1970 (Box 69)
    - J.B. and Dorothy C. Fuqua 1965 (Personal) Income Tax Schedule, 1965-1966 (Box 69)
    - Ford Motorcar Leasing Agreement for Company Car for Fuqua National, Inc., 1969 (Box 69)
    - Fuqua National Inc. Property Tax Receipts, 1963-1970 (Box 69)
    - Rentavision of Brunswick, Inc. - Balance Sheets and associated Mats., 1967-1968 (Box 69)
    - Changes in license application Folder - materials regarding 1960's FCC licence renewal, 1967-1969 (Box 70)
    - H -Miscellaneous (WJBF) Folder - Assorted Correspondence from/to Thomas Hennesy, Vice President, WJBF, 1960-1964 (Box 70)
    - Sunday Chronicle Herald, Nov. 9, 1969 article on an employee of WJBF and Oliver Hardy impersonator, 1969 (Box 70)
    - Video Binder - National Association of Broadcasters publication (Box 70)
    - NBC-Blue Network- Advance Program for week of December 1, 1940 (Box 70)
    - Study completed by J.B. Fuqua on the radio channels in the Greenville, SC, area, 1946 (Box 70)
    - Television Digest - Assorted copies from 7/2/1949-11/29/1952 (Box 70)
    - Television Factbook - 1/15/1951 (Box 70)
    - Television Rates and Factbook - 7/15/1950 (Box 70)
    - Correspondence from Mexican Imports Co. regarding Terrazzo installation, 8/23/1960 (Box 70)
    - Western Union Telegram from Fuqua to Torginol of America, 4/10/1964 (Box 70)
    - Ampex Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials to/from Ampex Corp supplier of AV materials, 1957-1964 (Box 70)
    - Barter Plans Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials regarding potential adverts for trade/service agreements, 1957-1966 (Box 70)
    - Equipment - Studio Folder - Assorted Corresp, Contracts, and Materials regarding purchase/sale of TV Studio Equip, 1964-1966 (Box 70)
    - Re: PETITION FOR WAIVER (Importation of Distant Signal) Folder - Assorted Correspondence & Materials regarding a company's plan to bring Comm. Antenna/Cable TV to Augusta, 1970-1974 (Box 71)
    - Completed Contracts Folder - Assorted Correspondence & Contract regarding aired specials and series, 1968-1971 (Box 71)
    - State Charter- Augusta Franchise - Maps Folder - Materials regarding Fuqua's bid for cable TV franchise in Augusta, 1968-1972 (Box 71)
    - Aircraft Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials regarding Fuqua Industries aircraft purchase, maintenance, etc., 1957-1967 (Box 72)
    - Aircraft Radio - File #1 Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Mat regarding Aircraft radio and radar equipment, 1961-1965 (Box 72)
    - Russian Tour Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials from/to travel agencies (etc.) regarding (potential?) trips to Europe and the USSR, 1956-1957 (Box 72)
    - World Travelers' Club Inc. Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials regarding Fuqua's membership in the World Travelers' Club, 1958-1960 (Box 72)
    - Hunting Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials regarding Hunting trips, 1960-1966 (Box 72)
    - Charleston WFAK Envelope - Application to the FCC and other associated correspondence/materials for/by Charleston Broadcasters and other business materials for WFAK, 1944-1948 (Box 72-73)
    - Tied Bundle of Assorted business materials relating to WFAK, Charleston, 1946-1948 (Box 72-73)
      Letter to Staff from JB Fuqua regarding Supervisor relations (In JB Fuqua WFAK Envelope).
    - Sims Publishing Company Folder - Application to the FCC and assoc correspondence/materials for/by Sims Publishing Co., 1944-1947 (Box 73)
    - Application to the FCC and associated correspondence for/by The Orangeberg Broadcasting Corp., 1944-1946 (Box 74)
    - Orangeburg WTND etc Envelope - Application for Class IV station and associated correspondence and materials., 1941-1948 (Box 74)
    - Study of Listening Habits: Augusta, Georgia prepared by Robert S. Conlan and Associates, 1948 (Box 74)
    - National Affairs - Merchandising Trends Newsletter, March 15, 1945 (Box 74)
    - Nashville (Tenn. Broadcasters) Greenville application Envelope - Application to FCC and assoc correspondence/materials for/by 1) Tennessee Broadcasters [Nashville] and 2) J.B. Fuqua [Greenville], 1943-1947 (Box 74)
    - Radio Folder - Misc. materials regarding Radio audiences and potential purchases, 1957-1964 (Box 74)
    - Photostat copy of contract of incorporation for National Fire Proofing Corporation in the state of Pennsylvania, 1929 (Box 75)
    - Appraisal of 3 TV stations (WUSN, WNCT, WECT) done by Blackburn and Co. and associated correspondence, 1960 (Box 75)
    - Tower application Folder - Correspondence and Materials regarding relocation of WJBF tower after fire of 8/56, 1957-1958 (Box 75)
    - Towers Folder - Correspondence and materials regarding purchase/construction of a transmitter tower, 1955-1956 (Box 75)
    - TV Contract File Folder - Nielsen Station Index Agreement, July 15, 1966 (Box 75)
    - WJBF - Charter Folder - Assorted materials regarding WJBF/Georgia-Carolina Broadcasting, 1949-1957 (Box 75)
      Response by plaintiff on an court action by the US Dept of Labor against Georgia-Carolina Broadcasting.
    - KTVE General Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials regarding KTVE-TV, El Dorado, Arkansas, 1963-1967 (Box 75)
      April 24, 1965, Letter from Thomas Hennesy to General Manager Of KTVE regarding his role at the station.
    - TV Applications Folder - Photostat reproductions of FCC Broadcasting applications by 4 different companies and associated materials, 1952-1953 (Box 76)
    - 1956-1957 New Tower, FCC, WNOK, WCSC, etc Envelope - FCC Correspondence by/against broadcast companies in opposition to WJBF's new tower, 1957 (Box 76)
    - Community Calendar January-December 1969 Folder - list of local events (Box 76)
    - Personnel Public Appearances, Etc. Folder - Personnel Profiles, list of places visited, and letters of appreciation, 1967-1969 (Box 76)
    - FCC Publication on the matter of Interim Policy on VHF Television Channel Assignment, 1960 (Box 76)
    - Map of Calculated additional interference to existing service which would be caused by suggested Milwaukee Channel 8 Drop-In (Box 76)
    - Announcement of Order regarding Interim Policy on VHF Television Channel Assignment, 1961 (Box 76)
    - Figures (Maps) regarding transmission area of WJBF and interference by drop-ins, 1961 (Box 76)
    - FCC Report and Order regarding Assignment of an Additional VHF Channel to multiple sites, 1961 (Box 76)
    - Report on audit of Radio Evansville, Inc. WROZ, Dec 31, 1965 (Box 76)
    - Non-network Television Broadcasting Report by Oppenheimer & Co., Nov. 20, 1964 (Box 76)
    - 1/23/62 Assoc of Maxi mum Service Telecasters Memo regarding FCC Order, Docket 14229 (Box 76)
    - Century Advertising Co. Comment on an issue before the FCC, Docket 14238, 1962 (Box 76)
    - Sale of KTVE Station Envelope - 6 unsigned copies of a Stock Re-Purchase Agreement, each with a different name on it, 1966 (Box 76)
    - Federal Communications Commission Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials regarding the FCC, 1952-1963 (Box 76)
    - Public Service Announcements 1969 Folder - Lists of PSAs for/by WJBF (Box 76)
    - Letters of Appreciation 1968 Folder - Correspondence from Assorted institutions thanking WJBF for their help by announcements, 1967-1969 (Box 76)
    - Collected letters of recommendation for Fuqua in nomination for Georgia Assoc of Broadcasters Broadcaster-Citizen of the Year Award, 1963 (Box 76)
    - WJBF Jan 65-Dec 69 Folder - Ledgers and associated financial materials regarding WJBF for period noted, 1965-1969 (Box 76)
    - Public Service Announcements 1968 Folder - Lists of PSAs for/by WJBF, 1968 (Box 77)
    - Reply Comment of WATE, Inc. - response from/by WATE-TV on potential order by FCC, 1962 (Box 77)
    - WEAU-TV Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials regarding WEAU-TV/Central Broadcasting Company, 1959-1961 (Box 77)
    - X-Y-Z -- Miscellaneous Folder - Letter from Asa Stallworth to Jeffrey Zients, 7/13/1966 (Box 77)
    - WAFB Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials regarding WAFB/Modern Broadcasting Co., Baton Rouge, 1963 (Box 77)
    - TV Folder - Assorted Correspondence regarding purchase of television programs/features, 1957-1963 (Box 77)
    - TV Results Folder - Sponsor Publication regarding results by advertisers using local TV, 1957 (Box 77)
    - Translators Folder - Assorted Correspondence and Materials regarding purchase of a VHF TV Translators, 1961-1966 (Box 77)